A-Ayatsuji-san?
（純一）あッ…　絢辻さん
（詞）勝手にしゃべらない
すッ　すみません
Don't talk without permission.
S-Sorry...
〈む　む…　胸が…〉
H... Her chest...
橘君　見ちゃったんだ
So you read it, Tachibana-kun.
そっか
I see...
I apologize if I offended you.
気に障ったんなら謝るよ
So just let me go!
だから　とにかく離れて
（二人）あッ…
ごッ　ごめん！
S-Sorry!
Could you come with me for a bit?
これから少し　つきあってくれる？
でも…
But...
Could you come with me?
つきあって　く・れ・る？
はッ…　はい
Y... Yes.
・～
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
君は君のままで
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
僕は僕のままで
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
全て分かり合えたら
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
何度も季節を重ねたね　あの日から
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
今日までどうもありがとう
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
狭い路地裏目指し
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
白い息が踊る
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
痛いくらい握った手をひいて
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
君は進んでいく
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
今すぐキスしたかった
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
隠れた自販機の裏
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
ハニかんで見つめあった
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
優しいキモチ溢れた
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
君は君のままで
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
僕は僕のままで
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
全て分かり合えたなら
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
２人は１つだよ
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
どんな小さな幸せも
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
見つけ出せる気がするよ
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
優しくなれたのは　君のおかげ
さてと　ここならゆっくり
話できるでしょ？
All right, we should be able to have a nice long chat here.
それじゃ　さっそく本題
あなた　これを見たのよね？
Now, on to the main subject.
You read this, didn't you?
Sorry.
ごめん　持ち主の名前が
書いてあるかと思って少しだけ
I thought I might find the owner's name inside, so just a little...
So that means you read the thing I scribbled...
それで　書きなぐったアレを
見ちゃったわけだ
残念だわ　クラスメートが一人
減っちゃうなんて
What a shame.
Sounds like I'm about to lose a classmate.
うん？　ちょっと待って
何よ
Wait a minute.
書きなぐったアレって何？
はあ？
What?
What do you mean, the thing you scribbled?
Huh?
I thought your handwriting was really neat...
キレイな字だな～とは思ったけど
Hang on...
待って　もう一度聞くわよ
Let me ask again.
You read what was inside this notebook, right?
あなた　手帳の中身を見たのよね？
うん
Yeah.
Which means you read the thing I scribbled.
それで　書きなぐったアレを見たと
だから　書きなぐったアレって何？
はあ？
Yeah, and I'm asking what you mean by that.
What?
僕が見たのはスケジュールと
メモ欄を少しだけなんだけど
All I saw was a schedule and some memos.
Huh?
えッ？
ひょっとして　勘違い？
Could this be a misunderstanding?
そうなんだ
うるさいわね
Oh, looks like it.
Shut up!
You weren't being clear.
あなたがちゃんと言わないから
言う暇なんてなかったじゃないか
You didn't give me a chance to.
If you didn't see anything, you
should've just said so loud and clear!
見てないなら見てないって
堂々としてなさいよ
It's your fault I read too deeply into this!
お陰で深読みしちゃったじゃない
だって…
But...
はあ…　まったく
Geez...
あのさ
何よ
Hey, uh...
What?
So... is your normal personality just an act?
もしかして　絢辻さん
普段は猫かぶってるの？
なッ…
W-
Heh, that was easy to see.
〈ああ～　わかりやすい〉
So what?
だから何　猫かぶってちゃ悪いの？
Ayatsuji Tsukasa Arc
Chapter 2
Inner Side
What's so bad about it?
それで私が誰かに
迷惑をかけたとでも？
Are you saying that I'll trouble others that way?!
ごめん　別に悪くないよ
Sorry, I'm not saying it's bad.
まあ　いいわ
Well, that's fine.
あなたが誰にも言わなければ
それで問題ないわけだし
It's not a problem as long as you don't tell anyone.
All right, repeat after me.
さあ　復唱して
僕は何も見ていません
"I saw nothing."
絢辻さんは　裏表のない
ステキな人です
"Ayatsuji-san is a wonderful person with nothing to hide."
えッ　何で僕が　そんなことを
Huh?  Why do I have to?
だって橘君　私の胸　触ったくせに
But Tachibana-kun, you touched my chest...
T-That was-
ああッ　あれは…
ひどいわ　私の純情が汚されたわ
You're horrible!
You've defiled my innocence!
I'll have to talk to your family and the teachers about this...
あなたの家族か先生にでも
相談しないと
わかった　わかりました
Okay, I get it.
I saw nothing, and uh...
僕は何も見てません　えっと…
"Ayatsuji-san is a wonderful person with nothing to hide."
「絢辻さんは　裏表のない
ステキな人です」
Ayatsuji-san is a wonderful person with nothing to hide.
絢辻さんは　裏表のない
ステキな人です
よろしい
Very good.
はあ
ご褒美に　もう一度触ってみる？
As a reward, how about touching it again?
ええッ！　それは　あの　えっと…
Huh?!
That's um... uh...
I'm obviously kidding.
冗談に決まってるでしょ！
あッ…　あははははッ
Geez, don't take that kind of thing seriously.
もう　本気にしないでよね
とにかく　あなたは何も見なかった
このことは誰にも言わない
Anyway, you saw nothing, and you'll say nothing.
わかった？
わかりました
Got it?
Understood.
それじゃ　話も済んだし
帰りましょう
All right.  Since that's taken care of, let's go home.
ああ　あの　一つ聞いてもいいかな
U-Uh, can I ask you something?
何？
What?
What exactly is the thing you scribbled?
なぐり書きのアレって
結局　何が書いてあったの？
ああ～　そうね
Ah, let's see.
見られたら私が学校に
いられなくなるようなこと　かな
I guess you could say it's something that'd
make me leave the school if someone read it.
And for that, I'll make sure the person who read it won't want to come back either.
その代わり　見た人も学校に
いられなくしてあげるけどね
ぼッ　僕は何も見ていません
I-I saw nothing!
絢辻さんは　裏表のない
ステキな人です
Ayatsuji-san is a wonderful person with nothing to hide!
はい　よくできました
Yes, very good indeed.
（美也）あれ　どうしたの？　にぃに
Huh?
What's wrong, Nii-nii?
Miya, there are things in this world we're better off not knowing.
美也　世の中には知らないほうが
幸せなことってあるんだな
Huh?
はあ？
Princess Nukata, one of the
representative poets of the Asuka period,
飛鳥時代の日本を代表する
歌人として知られる額田王は
恋多き女性としても
知られています
is also known as a woman who had many lovers.
〈絢辻さんに　あんな
裏の顔があるなんて言っても〉
Even if I told someone that
Ayatsuji-san has a hidden side to her,
〈きっと誰も信じないだろうな〉
I'm sure nobody would believe me.
Huh?
（梅原）はあ？　絢辻さんが
どうしたって？
What about Ayatsuji-san?
Well, the truth is, yesterday...
うん…　実は昨日
うん？
その…　昨日…
Um... yesterday...
Tachibana-kun.
橘君
うッ
Oh, speak of the devil.
おッ　ウワサをすれば
ウワサ？
What?
コイツが何か　絢辻さんのことで
話があるとか言ってさ
Oh, he was just telling me he had something to say about you.
ああ　ああ　ああ～ッ！
それなら　たぶん
Oh, he must be talking about my notebook.
手帳のことじゃないかな
手帳？
Notebook?
Yeah, Tachibana-kun found and returned the notebook I dropped yesterday.
うん　昨日　私が落とした手帳を
橘君が拾ってくれたの
What?  That's all it was?
何だ　そんな話か
ねえ　橘君
Hey, Tachibana-kun.
There's some committee stuff I'd like to talk to you about.
実行委員のことで
少し相談があるの
ちょっといいかな？
はッ　はい…
Do you have a moment?
Y-Yeah.
Boss, hang in there.
大将　頑張れよ
ああ
Yeah.
Founder's Festival
Planning Committee Headquarters
誰にも言わないって
約束したはずよね
Didn't you promise not to tell anybody?
うッ　うん
Y-Yeah...
So why were you about to tell Umehara-kun?
じゃあ　何で梅原君に
言おうとしたの？
Because...
それは
それは？
Because?
絢辻さんに
こんな一面があるって言っても
I wanted to see if anyone would believe me if I said that you had another side to you.
誰も信じない
だろうな～って思って　試しに
Right, so you wanted to see.
そう　試しになんだ
ごッ　ごめんなさい
I-I'm sorry!
まあ　いいわ
えッ　許してくれるの？
Well, whatever.
Huh?  You'll forgive me?
Forgive you?
許す？　もう二度と
変な気を起こさないように
I'll make sure you don't get any more funny ideas.
I'm going to have you work your butt off.
た～っぷりと
働いてもらうことにするわ
ああ…　ああ…
・～
57th Annual
Kibitou High School Founder's Festival
Courage   Camaraderie
Contact   Conventions
Event Date: 12/24
Event Location: Kibitou High School Grounds
はあ～　やっと今日の仕事終了っと
I'm finally done for the day!
あッ　もう　こんな時間か
Whoa, it's this time of night already?
It's gotten really late.
すっかり遅くなっちゃったな
うん？
お疲れさま
Nice work.
Ayatsuji-san, you're doing this too?
絢辻さん
こんなことまでしてたんだ
Here.
はい
ありがとう
Thanks.
Morishima-senpai said she wanted to do it so I let her, but it looks like she gave up halfway.
森島先輩が　やりたいっていうから
任せてたんだけど
途中で飽きちゃったみたい
So, Ayatsuji-san...
絢辻さんってさ
うん？
どうして　そんなに
創設祭の準備を頑張るの？
Hmm?
Why do you work so hard to prepare for the Founder's Festival?
Isn't that obvious?
決まってるじゃない　自分のためよ
はあ？
It's for my own sake.
Huh?
If things get delayed, my standing as the committee president will be damaged.
作業が遅れれば実行委員長である
私の評価にキズがつくわ
はあ
I obviously can't let that happen.
そんなの　絶対許せないじゃない
I'm trying to look perfect here.
私は完ぺきを求めてるの
はあ
Right.
それに
もともと仕切るのは好きだし
Besides, I like being in charge anyway.
クラス委員とか実行委員とか
やっておくと
Having held positions like class rep and committee
president will help me get recommendations for college.
推薦入試のとき有利になるのよ
You sure are looking out for yourself.
打算的だ
何よ　何か文句ある？
What?  You have a problem with that?
別に　そういうわけじゃないけど
N-No, that's not what I meant...
さてと　ごちそうさま
Anyway...
Thanks for this.
Ah, should I help?
僕も手伝おうか？
Huh?  You don't have to.
えッ？　別にいいわよ
でも
But...
橘君って変な人ね
えッ？
Tachibana-kun, you're weird.
Huh?
I mean, you know my secret, don't you?
だって　私の秘密を
知ってるわけでしょ？
If I were you, I'd distance myself from someone like me as much as I can.
私だったら　そんな人には
絶対に近づかないわ
何を考えてるのかも　わからないし
You have no idea what I'm thinking about.
近づくことに
何の得も見いだせないもの
There aren't any clear benefits from being with me.
Yet you offer to help me and bring me refreshments, all by yourself.
なのに橘君は
自分から手伝うとか言いだしたり
差し入れしてくれたりして
ねえ　どうして？
So why?
You're asking me why?
どうしてと言われても
うん…　そうだな
Let's see...
Because it's fun, I guess.
楽しいからかな
楽しい？
Fun?
Yeah.
うん　絢辻さん手際もいいし
一緒にやってて　結構楽しいよ
You're really talented, so it's pretty fun to do all this together.
And while there's lots to do every day,
the more I work the more fulfilling it gets...
それに　毎日忙しいけど
その分だけ充実してるっていうか
実行委員の仕事も
おもしろくなってきたし
The committee work is also proving to be very interesting.
そう　ふ～ん
I see.
Hmm...
Hey, I think I'll help after all.
ねえ　やっぱり僕も手伝うよ
いいって言ってるでしょ
Didn't I already say you don't have to?
でも　絢辻さん　昨日もおとといも
遅くまで残ってたよね
But Ayatsuji-san, didn't you stay behind yesterday and the day before?
いいから早く帰って寝なさい
Whatever, just go home and sleep!
Don't forget that you are part of the
Founder's Festival planning committee!
あなたは仮にも
創設祭実行委員なのよ
If you fall asleep in class again...
また授業中に居眠りでもしたら…
...your standing as the committee president will be damaged?
実行委員長としての
絢辻さんの評価にキズがつく？
そういうこと
わかってきたじゃない
Exactly right.
So you do understand.
Well then, see you tomorrow.
じゃ　また明日ね
了解
Gotcha.
Hmm... is it just me?
〈何だろう　気のせいかな〉
〈絢辻さん　まるで家に帰るのを
嫌がってるみたい〉
It's like Ayatsuji-san doesn't want to go home...
あ～あ　おはよ
Morning.
Ah Junichi, you're finally here!
・（薫）あッ　純一　やっと来た
何だよ　薫　朝っぱらから慌てて
Why are you freaking out so early in the morning, Kaoru?
何のんきなこと言ってんの　大変よ
How can you be so calm?  This is serious!
What's serious?
大変って　何が？
絢辻さんが過労で倒れたんだって
Ayatsuji-san passed out from working too hard!
はあ？
Huh?
I'm pretty sure Ayatsuji-san's house is around here.
この辺りだよな　絢辻さんの家
Here, come on.
（縁）ほれほれ
あの
あら？　こんにちは
Uh...
Oh?  Good afternoon.
どうも　こんにちは
Hello, and good afternoon.
えっと　確か詞ちゃんのお友達の
タカハシ君
Um... you must be Tsukasa-chan's friend, Takahashi-kun.
橘です
そうそう　橘君
I-It's Tachibana.
Ah, that's right.  Tachibana-kun.
Ooh, are you visiting Tsukasa-chan?
ああッ　もしかして詞ちゃんに
お見舞い？
ええ　まあ
Yeah, I guess...
Ah, but if Tsukasa-san isn't feeling very well at all...
でも　もし詞さんの体調が
悪いようでしたら
これを　お姉さんから
渡していただけますか？
Could you please give this to her?
I... don't really know how she's feeling.
体調どうだろう　詞ちゃん
あんまり　しゃべらないから
Tsukasa-chan hasn't been talking very much.
そうなんですか
I see.
せっかく　来てくれたんだから
顔を見ていってあげて
You're already here anyway, so you might as well go see her.
うちは　すぐそこだから
ええッ　でも…
Our home is right there too.
Um, but...
It's all good.
いいから　いいから　体調のことも
本人に聞くのが一番だしね
It's best that you ask her how she's feeling face-to-face!
ああ　ちょっと　ちょっと　お姉さん
W-Wait, Onee-san!
Tsukasa-chan?
・（縁）詞ちゃん　詞ちゃん
Tsukasa-chan.
・（縁）ぐっすり
眠っちゃってるみたいね
Looks like she's fast asleep.
（ドアが閉まる）
まったく　少しは静かに
寝かせてくれないかしら
Geez, couldn't she just let me sleep in peace?
Ah, I'm really sweaty.
ああ　汗かいちゃった
あッ？
ああ　ああ…
こッ　こッ　これには事情が
T-T-There's an explanation for this...
うわ～ッ！
Wait, listen to me!
待って　話を聞いて！
はあ…　そう　あの人が
I see, that woman...
Yeah.  She said I should at least see you since I'm already here.
うん　ここまで来たんだから
顔を見てけって
まったく　いつもいつも勝手に
Damn it, she's always doing whatever she wants...
ごめん　すぐ帰るよ
Sorry, I'll leave right away.
You don't have to.
いいわよ　もう
お見舞い　ありがとう
Thanks for visiting me.
女の子相手に　バナナと栄養ドリンク
っていうのは　どうかと思うけど
Though I don't know what to think about you bringing bananas and energy drinks for a girl.
あはははッ
過労って聞いたんで
I heard you overworked yourself, so I
thought these would help you recover.
体力を回復するなら
こういうのかと思って
それより　体調のほうはどう？
Anyway, how are you feeling?
I'm fine.
平気　少し熱が出ただけだから
I just have a light fever, so I should be able to go to school tomorrow.
明日には学校に行けると思うわ
そっか～　よかった
I see... that's a relief.
あなたって本当に変な人ね
えッ？
You really are a weirdo.
Huh?
I'm saying you're a weirdo.
変な人って言ったの
あははッ　そうかな～
Am I now?
Though, your sister's personality is also pretty unique, Ayatsuji-san.
でも　絢辻さんのお姉さんも
個性的だよね
うん？　ええ～
What?
何か　ポワポワっとしてるって
いうか
It's like she's zoned out...
Or you could say she's lost in her own world...
浮世離れしてるっていうか
She feels like a totally different person from you, Ayatsuji-san.
雰囲気も絢辻さんと全然違うし
そうね
I see.
Ayatsuji-san, your sister...
絢辻さんのお姉さんってさ…
ごめん　私少し寝るわ
Sorry, I'm going to sleep for a bit.
ああッ　うん
Ah, okay.
Sorry I stayed for so long.
長居してごめんね
それじゃあ僕　帰るよ
Well, I'm off.
橘君
うん？
Tachibana-kun.
Thanks for visiting me.
お見舞い　ありがとう
ううん　お大事に
It's cool.  Take care.
Oh?  Going home already?
あら　もう帰るの？
どうも　お邪魔しました
Hello.  Thanks for having me over today.
もっと　ゆっくりしていけば
いいのに
You could've stayed just a little longer.
I shouldn't stay for too long.
あんまり長居しても悪いですから
Is Tsukasa-chan awake?
・（縁）詞ちゃん　起きた？
はい
Yes.
少し話をして
今はまた寝るって言ってました
We talked a little, and she just said that she's gonna sleep some more.
How is she?
具合　どうだって？
少し熱が出ただけで　明日には
学校に来れるって言ってました
She said that she just has a light fever and should be able to go to school tomorrow.
そうなんだ
I see!
By the way Onee-san, what are you doing?
ところで　お姉さんは
何をしてるんですか？
ああ　詞ちゃんに
スポーツドリンク買ってきたんだけど
Oh, I bought this sports drink for Tsukasa-chan,
but she doesn't want it, so I'm giving it to this dog instead.
詞ちゃん　飲んでくれないから
代わりに犬にあげてたの
橘君　飲む？
いえ　結構です
Tachibana-kun, do you want it?
No, I'm fine.
I see.
そう　ねえ　最近の野良犬って
人に懐かないように
You know, I wonder if stray dogs nowadays have been trained not to warm up to people.
教育とか　されてるのかな
はあ？
Huh?
He isn't warming up to me at all.
全然懐いてくれないんだよね
そッ　そうですか
I-I see.
Uh... well, I'll be going now.
あの　じゃあ僕は　これで
うん
Okay.
またね
See you.
〈絢辻さんとあの人が姉妹だなんて
ちょっと信じられないな〉
It's a little hard to believe that she and Ayatsuji-san are sisters.
Actually, it looks like Ayatsuji-san doesn't like her sister very much...
〈というか
絢辻さんお姉さんのこと〉
〈あまり
好きじゃないみたいだったし〉
〈なんだか複雑そうだな〉
This looks complicated.
（あくび）
Morning, Tachibana-kun.
おはよう　橘君
おはよう　絢辻さん
よかった　元気になったんだね
Morning, Ayatsuji-san.
I'm glad you recovered.
ええ　昨日も言ったでしょ
すぐによくなるって
Yes, didn't I say that I'd recover soon enough yesterday?
でももしかしたらバナナと栄養ドリンクが
効いたのかもしれないわね
But it's possible that the bananas and the energy drinks worked.
それなら
持っていった甲斐があったよ
Then I guess it's a good thing I brought them over.
Whoa, it's Morishima-senpai!
・（生徒Ａ）森島先輩だ
・（Ｂ）何で二年の階に
What's she doing on the junior-year floor?!
Tsukahara-senpai's here too!
・（Ｃ）塚原先輩もいるぞ
・（Ｄ）朝からラッキーだぜ
What a lucky morning!
Do you have a moment?
（響）ちょっといいかしら
朝早くから　ごめんなさい
Sorry for disturbing you this early in the morning.
I'd like to ask the committee president about something regarding the Founder's Festival.
創設祭のことで実行委員長さんに
ちょっと聞きたいことがあるの
What is it, Tsukahara-senpai?
何ですか？　塚原先輩
その…
はい
Well...
Yes.
実は…
うん？
The truth is...
Hmm?
（二人）うん？
（はるか）はあ…
もう　じれったいな
Geez, I can't wait anymore!
The truth is, Hibiki decided to come out of her shell and create a final high school memory.
実は　響が自分の殻を破って
高校最後の思い出作りに
She finally decided to participate in the Miss Santa contest!
ミスサンタコンテストに出ようかなって
やっと決心したの
ちょっと　はるか
Wait, Haruka!
Tsukahara-senpai is...?
The Miss Santa contest?!
それで　せっかくだから
ビキニを着たらって私が勧めたの
Since this is pretty rare, I suggested that she wear a bikini or something.
Something naughty like this!
こ～んな　きわどいやつとか
えッ！？
Huh?!
A... A naughty bikini?!
こッ　こんなきわどいビキニ！？
Ouch!
痛～ッ！
Ayatsuji-san, you're stepping on my foot!
絢辻さん　足踏んでる！
あら　ごめんなさい
Ooh, I'm sorry.
Well, I'm worried Haruka'll make me wear
something incredible if I leave it to her to decide,
あのね　はるかに任せると
すごい格好させられそうだから
規定みたいなものがあるなら
確かめておこうと思ったの
so I thought I'd confirm with you if there are any rules and the like.
で　どうなの？　コンテストの衣装って
どこまで許されるのかしら
So... well?
Just how far can we go with the costumes for the contest?
響は　背中からおしりのラインが
キレイだから
Hibiki's curves from her back to her ass are really nice, so we'll definitely want to expose them!
そこは　ぜひ出したいのよね
Her curves from her back to her ass?!
背中からおしりのライン！？
Ouch!
痛～ッ！
Ayatsuji-san, you're stepping on my foot again!
絢辻さん　また足踏んでる！
あら　ごめんなさい
Ooh, I'm sorry.
I see.
そうですね　高校のお祭りですし
学外の方も　おみえになりますので
It's a high school festival, so people from outside this school will be present.
I'd appreciate it if you'll avoid going for something too daring.
あまり大胆な格好は遠慮して
いただきたいところですけど
ええ～ッ
Come on...
でも　絶対にダメということでは
ないですよ
But I'm not saying you can't at all.
Okie-dokie!
Ｏｋｉｅ－ｄｏｋｉｅ！
やったわ　そうこなくっちゃ
We did it!  That's what we need!
However, please keep it reasonable.
ただし　あくまで
常識の範囲内でお願いします
W-We understand.
・（響）わかったわ
This year's Miss Santa contest is going to be amazing!
〈今年のミスサンタコンテストは
すごいことになりそうだ〉
（チャイム）
よっとっとと…
しかし　何でサバの段ボールなんて
必要なんだ
Though, why do we need mackerel cardboard boxes?
何に使うのか
まったく予想がつかないな
I have absolutely no idea what they'll be used for...
ああ～ッ！
That cry...!
今の声
はあ…
Ayatsuji-san!
絢辻さん！
橘君
Tachibana-kun.
何があったの？
別に何もないわよ
What happened?
N-Nothing, really.
Did you hurt your foot?
もしかして　足にケガとかしたの？
見せて
Lemme see.
絢辻さん
何よ
Ayatsuji-san.
What?
何で足がぬれてるの？
Why is your foot wet?
Ayatsuji-san?
絢辻さん？
かけられたの
...on me.
えッ？
オシッコを　ひっかけられたのよ
He urinated on me.
ええ～ッ　誰に！？
バカ！　犬に決まってるでしょ
W-Who did?!
Idiot!  A dog, obviously!
い…　犬？
A... A dog?
校内で高そうな犬を見かけたから
I saw this expensive-looking dog on the school grounds.
I thought that I could probably use him for something, so I tried to catch him.
何か使い道があるんじゃないかと
思って　捕まえようとしたの
And then he really warmed up to me...
そしたら　妙に懐かれて
Ah, dogs urinate when they're happy.
ああ～　犬ってうれしいと
オシッコしちゃったりするから
あはははッ　それは災難だったね
This is quite the disaster!
This isn't funny.
笑い事じゃないんですけど
ごめん
S-Sorry.
はい
えッ　何？
Here.
Huh?
What?
何って　おんぶだよ
はあ？
What else?  I'm carrying you.
Huh?!
だって　そのままじゃ
どうしようもないでしょう
I mean, not like we can do anything about this here.
We'll need to wash your shoes and stuff, so I'll carry you to the taps.
靴下とか洗わなきゃいけないし
水道まで　おぶっていくよ
What'll people say if they see us like this?!
こんなとこ誰かに見られたら　何を
言われるか　わからないじゃない
It doesn't matter what people'll say.
何を言われても別にいいよ
事情が事情だし
We have nothing to hide.
I'm not fine with this!
私がよくないの
わかった　ごめん
Okay, I'm sorry.
Just stay still, or you'll fall!
だから暴れないで　落ちちゃうよ
よっと
うわッ
変なところ触らないでよ
Where do you think you're groping?!
B-But I'm not groping...
触ってないよ
変態
Pervert!
もう　お好きなように
Whatever, say what you want.
Everyone, there's a pervert right here!
みなさ～ん
ここに変態がいますよ～
Actually, please give me a break.
やっぱり　勘弁してください
ダメ
Nope!
But someone might see us if you make too much noise.
でも　あんまり騒ぐと　誰かに
見られちゃうかもしれないよ
はあ～
橘君　本当に不思議な人
Tachibana-kun's a real mystery.
〈私とは違う価値観を
持ってるのかな〉
Maybe it's because he has different values than I do?
〈ちょっと気になるかも〉
I'm a little curious.
〈あれ　そういえば
私が誰かを気にするなんて〉
Huh?  Thinking about it, isn't this the first time I've ever been curious about someone?
〈もしかして初めてじゃない？〉
〈変なの
もしかして　詞　お気に入り？〉
How strange.
Hey there Tsukasa, don't tell me you're interested in him?
あッ　もう何考えてんだろう　私
Geez, what the heck am I thinking?!
Ahh, it's Tachibana-kun's fault that I'm losing my studying time!
ああ～　橘君のせいで
勉強する時間が減ってるじゃない
もう～　あったまきた
Geez, I'm mad!
I'm really going to toy with you next time!
今度から
もっといじめてやるんだから
Step Up
For Dummies
Math II
Question Book
覚悟してなさいよ
Prepare yourself!
・～
Hodou wo kazaru aoi Illumination
The blue illumination adorns the sidewalk
歩道を飾る　青いイルミネーション
Nigiwau hitogomi ni hitori tatazumu
And I stand alone in the swarming crowd
にぎわう人込みにひとりたたずむ
Koboresou na egao
Smiles peeking through
こぼれそうな笑顔
Yorisou koibitotachi
Lovers snuggling against each other
寄り添う恋人達
Ima no watashi ni wa subete ga
Everything to me now is so bright
今の私には全てが
Mabushikute mirenai no
That I cannot bear to look
まぶしくて見れないの
Dareka ni aisareru deshou ka
Will anyone love me?
誰かに愛されるでしょうか
Tsuyogari no oku ni kakureta
I'm hiding underneath a facade
強がりの奥に隠れた
Watashi ni kizuite yo
Please realize that
「わたし」に気付いてよ
Hontou ni jiyuu ni nareru deshou ka
Can I really become free?
本当に自由になれるでしょうか
Douka oshiete
Please tell me
どうか教えて
Fuyu no machi ni mayoikonda
Having lost her way in the winter town
冬の町に迷い込んだ
Samishige na tenshi ga nageku
The lonely angel sighs
さみしげな　天使が嘆く
Yasashiku
Gently
優しく
Preview
Next episode preview!
Tachibana-senpai, you seem happy.
How do I say this, isn't it nice to find a sense of fulfillment through hard work?
Let's see... I don't know if working too hard is a good thing,
but I do enjoy doing housework quite a bit.
Ooh Nanasaki, you're more domestic than I thought.
R-Really?
All right, I'm gonna work even harder on the committee stuff!
Next Episode
Pride
Next episode: "Pride".
Senpai, be sure to follow up after Ayatsuji-senpai.
Huh?  Oh, but of course!